Zachary Upstone

Email: Zac.upstone@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zachary-upstone-076218214/

Telephone: 07591 701760 Website: https://zupstn.com

Personal Profile

I am a recent graduate with a 1st in Computer Science from the University of Bath. I have experience working in both software development and quality assurance at BSQUARE an IoT solutions company. From this, I also gained experience working within a team in an agile environment developing my communication skills. I also have experience working multiple customerfacing job at McDonalds and a bar making me into a adaptable and enthusiastic worker who is good at handling people. I am also a team worker having experience working on group projects throughout university, this also shows that I am reliable and trustworthy.

Education

2020 - 2024

University of Bath – Computer Science BSc – First Class Honours.Overall grade – 74.51%

Units including:

- Final year project (Dissertation) 71% titled "Human Involvement Can Improve Current Image Synthesis Methods within the Domain of Art" explored using human feedback to improve current AI image generation techniques in a manner similar to ChatGPT, this was implemented in Python.
- Logic and semantics of programming languages 81% I studied how category theory relates to the underlying logic of programming languages, including the lambda calculus and closed cartesian categories.
- Entrepreneurship 72% Working as a team we started a company and developed a business plan selling services within a student community.
- **Graphs and Networks: Theory and Applications** 73% I studied a Maths modules based around graph theory.
- Reinforcement learning 71% Working as a group, we implemented DQN, RAINBOW and PPO in Python to solve the lunar lander environment in OpenAl's gym.
- Advanced graphics processing 89% From scratch I developed a ray tracer in C++, implementing reflection, refraction and other lighting effects, to create a realistic generated image.
- **Safety-critical systems** 79% I studied case studies of system's shortcomings in relation to safety in the past and how to mitigate or prevent such problems in the future.

2013 - 2020

Chesham Grammar School

A level: Further Mathematics (A), Mathematics (A*), Computer Science (A), Physics (A).

GCSE's: 4 grades 9's, 2 grade 8's, 3 grades 6's, 1 grade 5, 1 grade A.

Work Experience

July 2022 - June 2023

- Student software developer at BSQUARE, during my degree, I had a yearlong placement at BSQUARE, in which I worked 6 months in the development team for SquareOne in which I fixed bugs, produced new features (such as an OS updates page and a tour for

	a product) and tested code during QA sprints and 6 months in the QA team in which I wrote automated tests (for API and UI), performed manual tests and managed the delegation of manual testing during the QA sprint.
Nov 2021 - June 2022	 Bar staff at the Students Union at the University of Bath, I dealt with customers requests serving drinks, cleaning and operating a till. I had to use communication skills and be adaptable to new jobs.
July 2021 - Oct 2021	 Crew member at McDonalds, I worked at multiple station in McDonalds showing flexibility and ability to work in a team. This required good communication within the team in case I was needed at different stations.
July 2020 - Sept 2020	 Assistant Gardener at RM Gardening, this included manual labour and dealing with customers' requests developing my tenacity and adaptability to different workplace environments.
Other Experience	
Nov 2018 - Mar 2020	 Volunteered at WorkAid a tool repair shop for 18 months, In which I learned to fix knitting machines and gained skills in organisation and problem solving.
July 2019	 1 Week work experience at the Audit Bureau of Circulations in various departments reviewing magazines authenticity and managing IT issues which helped me understand how a team of people is coordinated.
June 2018	 2 Weeks at the IT help desk at Close Brother Asset Management assisting with various jobs, including network problems, software installation/setup and sorting hardware appliances. This helped develop my team communication and people skills.
Technical skills	develop my team communication and people skills.
Toormour Skins	- Experience with C++, Java and Python from my degree
	 Experience with Angular (TS, HTML, CSS), Selenium, and Gherkin from BSQUARE
	 Experience working in an agile environment and using Jira from BSQUARE
	 Experience with React from personal projects and hackathons Experience working in a team from McDonalds and BSQUARE Customer service skills from SU bar
	- Customer service skills from 50 bar - Full UK driver's license
Achievements	. dii Git diivoi o liooiloo
	- Gold DofE, in which I completed two expeditions hiking in the Brecor
	beacons and Snowdonia.
	 Competed in BathHack 2021 and 2024 using React both times
	producing web games.
lata a a ta	- Employee of the month August 2021 at McDonalds
<u>Interests</u>	There are the second to see the second to see the second to see the second to see the second to
	I have a keen interest in art and design producing prints using spray techniques as well as collages and clay sculptures. I am also interested in exercise going to the gym and swimming multiple times a week.
<u>References</u>	
	Hannah Stainer Operations manager at BSQUARE HannahS@bsquare.com Alan Hayes Personal tutor at the University of Bath AH347@bath.ac.uk